myrateplan.com 2008-06-22

# MyRatePlan.com - (Privacy Policy)

MyRatePlan.com, LLC (MRP) takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our policy. 

**Personal Information Collection**

  * No registration, and no personally identifiable information, such as name, address, e-mail address, or phone number is required for the use of MRP. 
  * Our collection of personal information is only asked for when needed to fulfill a specific user request. Examples include a direct purchase from MRP (such as an e-book), or when signing up for a specific information service (such as e-mail notification of local satellite TV channels in your area, or to enter a sweepstakes). 
    * When we collect personal information from you, it is only used for the specific purpose for which you request. We do not rent, sell or share personal information under any circumstances. We do not use personal information provided to us for one purpose for any other internal purpose (e.g., we will not add your name to any e-mail newsletters). 
      * An exception would be made in response to the investigation of fraud, a subpoena or other court order. 
  * As part of our effort to limit excessive e-mails, MRP does not collect e-mail addresses for any newsletters, and does not send out any newsletters. If that policy changes, we will update this privacy policy. 
    * When MRP has collected newsletter names in the past, it has used a double opt-in approach, requiring the user to reconfirm an intention to join the list. MRP also provided an automatic link to instantly opt-out of the mailing list. These privacy practices will be established again should MRP start an e-mail newsletter or similar e-mail program. 
  * Any personal information gathered is stored on secure servers. MRP has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alternation of the information under our control. MRP takes reasonable precaution not to allow access to the personal information contained within our databases. 
  * In most cases, MRP is not the retailer in a purchase transaction made through the MRP site. Therefore, the MRP site contains links to other sites where purchases or additional information can be gathered. MRP is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

**Cookies & IP Addresses**

  * MRP automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address. This information is used in the aggregate to help us manage site performance. 
  * MRP may set cookies on your computer. A cookie is an anonymous unique identifier. This allows us to make your future visits to MRP more convenient by retaining relevant information that you provide (e.g., your zip code for a wireless phone lookup). 
    * You can configure your browser to manage whether you want to accept cookies. Accepting cookies is not required to use MRP. 

**Children**

  * MRP does not market to children under 13, or collect information from children under 13 to enable them to access the MRP site. 
  * MRP does not anticipate marketing to, or requiring information from children under 13 in the future. Any change in that policy will be fully documented in an update to this privacy policy, and will be in full compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998. 
    * Parents wishing to get more information on COPPA and children's privacy may visit the [FTC web site](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm). 

**Opt-Out**

  * You may request, at any time, that we remove personal information that you have provided as part of a specific user request. We will remove your information from our databases, generally within 24 hours. o If you request removal, we will no longer be able to provide you with the service you have requested (e.g., sweepstakes entry or e-mail notification of an event). 
  * To remove any personal information from our databases, please [e-mail us](mailto:privacy@myrateplan.com). It will be helpful if you can include the information you had requested from us, so we can more quickly locate and remove your information from the appropriate table. 

Updated: January 31, 2005
